(The tassel crowns the knight. The sword is snow white.)
(In the silver saddle, he rides like a shooting star.)
(He kills a man within ten steps. Invincible he is all the way ahead.)
(He would leave once it's done. No trace of him is to be found.)
=Sword Snow Stride= (Season 1)
=Episode 11=
This is the transmission of Dahuangting.
Sure enough, Wudang has pledged allegiance to North Liang.
Your Grace.
This is our chance now.
How is that?
If we stop them now,
the internal force will render Xu Fengnian's meridians disorderly,
and he will be ruined.
Just a moment, Your Grace.
But if you do this,
Xu Xiao will hate you.
How can we depend on Xu Xiao?
Good.
If you make it,
the court will issue a decree
and make you the master of Wudang.
Thanks.
Let's do it together.
Who is that?
Brother Wang.
How did you come out of the Purple Bamboo Forest?
Don't go any farther.
If we don't stop them,
Master Chonglou will lose all his force.
It's his own decision.
There isn't much time left.
It's done.
It's too late.
Your Grace.
It's destined that it can't be done.
Let's go.
You ruined Wudang!
Little Taoist.
Do you want to come down with us?
Your Grace.
I won't go with you.
Master Chonglou lost all his force.
Wudang will elect a new master.
I'd like to try it.
If I could be the master,
maybe I could turn the tide.
Very good.
Rest assured.
The court will fully support you to take over Wudang.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Xu Fengnian will wake up soon.
Please leave as soon as possible.
Um.
You acted well.
There was more action than talk.
It was not that difficult.
Let's check Master Chonglou.
Master Chonglou.
Did it go well?
The Princess should have believed it.
Use the force of North Liang as a deterrent to Mount Longhu,
then with the support of the capital,
it will be a sure thing
for you to take over Wudang.
Master Chonglou.
Don't be sullen.
Use my Dahuangting
to change for the future for Wudang.
It's worth it.
Do you know why
the Shentu Sword
was given to you?
To guard Wudang.
The world is turbulent.
Before you become the best in the world,
we must count on you
to guard Wudang
with this mahogany sword.
I'll live and die
with Wudang.
You go up first.
Gather your fellow apprentices.
I have something to say.
What about you, Master Chonglou?
I'll wait for him to wake up.
Go ahead.
Your Grace.
We've seen no pursuers.
Let's go back to the capital now.
Yes, Your Grace.
Should we send a message
to the capital right now
that Xu Fengnian got the internal force?
Xu Fengnian is nothing but a fool.
So what that he acquired martial arts?
In terms of the momentum of history,
one person's capability
is not worth mentioning.
You are quite right, Your Grace.
Send the message about Wudang back now.
One thing is for sure
that Wudang has defected to North Liang.
Ask Mount Longhu not to be too aggressive.
We can't provoke Xu Xiao
just for a little sect.
Yes, Your Grace.
I will send a message to the capital immediately.
Um.
And also,
Hong Xixiang's heart is with the capital.
We should support him
to take over Wudang.
Why are my clothes not wet?
The water has been evaporated.
You lit a fire?
The genuine spirit works better than fire.
You've passed Dahuangting to me?
Yes.
I don't feel any difference.
Looks like you are compatible with my genuine spirit.
As for how much of the genuine spirit you can keep,
it depends on your fate.
Thank you.
You want to go up to the mountain?
Let me help you.
Thank you.
In order to protect Wudang,
I threw
my life away.
Wudang
is not a big sect, but it's not small, either.
It's even hard for us to survive in this world.
How hard the lives would be
for the common people?
If one day
you take over North Liang,
please
consider them.
I will.
Why are you waiting here?
To help you go up the mountain.
Good.
Then I won't trouble Your Highness.
Yeah.
It's almost the end of the year.
You should go back to North Liang.
You knew about the passing of Dahuangting?
Please
don't waste it.
I'll wait for the news that you set foot in Wudi City.
Come on.
Your Grace.
Um.
I'll get some hot water
to make tea for you.
Why are you following me?
You should guard Her Grace now!
Yes.
Fill it with hot water.
How is it going?
Things have changed.
What happened?
That person was taken away by the people of Mount Longhu.
It should be written by Jian Jiuhuang.
And His Highness...
What's wrong with His Highness?
Wang Chonglou
passed Dahuangting to him.
Princess Suizhu has believed
that Wudang has pledged allegiance to North Liang.
To protect themselves?
Aside from this accident,
everything else went on just as you expected.
Princess Suizhu
saw with her own eyes that His Highness is obstreperous and stupid.
From now on,
the capital won't be wary of His Highness.
By the way.
Father wants me to ask you
if you want to find a chance
to go back to North Liang.
My stay in the capital
will help His Lordship more.
Thank you.
I'll leave.
Your Grace.
We are ready to go.
Did you pay for it?
Yes.
Five pennies.
It's not easy for these people.
Send five more pennies to the owner.
(Tea)
Sir.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
Your tip.
Thank you very much.
Your Grace.
The money has been given to him.
Let's go.
Yes.
Sun Diaosi is right.
Princess Suizhu
is suspicious deep down
in spite of her unruly behavior.
Don't leave anything!
Burn everything you see!
Let's go to Wudang
and take His Highness home!
Wang Chonglou is daring indeed.
I wasn't expecting this, either.
Two months is up.
I should probably leave.
You won't go back to North Liang with me?
Everyone has his path.
We have to say goodbye
to those we meet on the way.
This is the world of martial arts.
Thank you for your teachings.
Keep practicing martial arts.
Maybe we will meet again.
I'm leaving.
(Sanqing Hall)
Here you are.
- Master. - Master.
Good.
From today on,
Wudang has
survived the calamity of extermination.
I only have one thing to tell you.
After my death,
Hong Xixiang
will take over Wudang and become the master.
Master Chonglou.
I think I can't erase it.
This is Dahuangting.
Jiang Ni.
Do you think I shouldn't have come to Wudang?
Don't complain when it's in your interest.
Pass it to me if you don't want it.
I'll die if I pass it to you.
That would be the best.
Besides, I don't know how to pass it.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, have you missed me?
I miss you so much!
Your Highness!
Jiang Ni.
It's time to go home.
Your Highness!
Fatty Lushan is coming!
You can stay here for a few more days if you want.
Your Highness!
That won't be necessary.
Master Wang said
it will take him too long to go down the mountain,
so he won't come to bid farewell.
Tell him for me
I won't forget
what I owe Wudang.
Um.
This is Wudang's book on practicing genuine spirit.
(Treatise of the Most Exalted One) You have Dahuangting now.
(Treatise of the Most Exalted One) It might help you.
Goodbye then.
Here is one thing.
Don't tear down the hut
and grow some vegetables for me
in the garden.
What kind of vegetables?
Just like before.
Do you want me to steal vegetables again?
You're the next master.
It's not hard.
You'd better leave now.
What?
Do you know how to ride a horse?
I don't. So what?
Nothing.
Eh!
Get down!
How do you go back to North Liang
if I get down?
I'll learn by myself.
I've restored the hut and the garden for you.
It has nothing to do with me.
I have one more thing to ask you before I leave!
Go ahead.
When exactly are you going to Jiangnan?
You don't even have the courage to see my sister?
When I become the best in the world,
I will be able to go down the mountain.
After I go down the mountain,
I'll go to see her.
The best in the world?
How long will it take?
It's gonna happen.
Let's go back to North Liang.
They've left.
Um.
They asked you to go to Jiangnan?
Master Chonglou.
I do like Xu Zhihu.
Um.
But I also like Wudang.
I'm not going to leave here
until I become the best in the world.
It must be hard for you.
It's not hard.
I'm just worried
that you place all your hope on me,
but what if I can't be the best in the world?
Eh?
We haven't had a match for years.
Well.
Why don't we do it today?
I don't think it's a good idea.
Are you scared?
Let's do it then.
Okay.
Well, Master Chonglou.
I'm more energetic than you, right?
I don't have Dahuangting anymore.
That was a glorious defeat.
What does that
have anything to do with Dahuangting?
Xixiang.
Just feel free to be yourself.
Our master and I won't make a mistake.
You will be the best in the world.
When you come down the mountain,
you must leave in a grand way
and make me
look good!
Okay!
The best in the world!
(Apricot Flower Wine Shop)
You're finally back, Your Highness.
Is this the mark of Dahuangting?
It looks good on you.
Do you all know it?
We got the message.
Congratulations on being endowed with civil and martial virtues.
You must be tired.
Please get inside and have some rest.
Eh?
Why are you all waiting outside?
Something happened in the mansion.
Let's go inside first.
Son.
You are finally back.
Wang Chonglou
is decisive indeed.
He actually passed his Dahuangting to you.
Never mind.
You must be hungry now.
Look what I got for you.
There are more.
I found this good stuff for you.
I don't want to eat.
What happened in the mansion?
What are you doing here?
Your Highness.
It's nothing serious.
Just to stay away from trouble.
Stay away from trouble?
The Lord of North Liang came here to stay away from trouble?
Is there a ghost in the mansion?
I wish
it was a ghost.
Your second sister is back.
You told her that I'm learning martial arts?
Do I need to tell her?
The whole world knows it now.
I'd better go back to Wudang and stay there for a few days.
Wait, wait, you can't leave.
Listen.
I've told her
that you're on your way back to North Liang.
She is waiting for you at home.
Xu Xiao!
You sold me out!
I have to save
one of us.
It's not necessary.
Do you see her?
She should be in my yard.
Go back to your rooms.
I'll go to see her myself.
Stay here!
(Xu Weixiong, the second daughter of the Lord of North Liang)
You're back to spend the New Year?
(Artificers' Record) I made you a set of pieces with rocks
(Artificers' Record) in Wudang.
Take a look.
You must be tired of reading.
Let me massage your shoulders.
Are you getting used to
the life at Shangyin Academy?
I heard you are learning martial arts.
Old Huang died in Wudi City.
I want to take his sword box back.
You think it's bad to learn martial arts?
- It's up to you. - Um.
I just didn't expect
that Old Huang is more important to you
than North Liang.
Why do you say that?
Right now,
you haven't even decided to take over the army of Xu.
I don't think I'm up to
such an important task.
Enough!
Weixiong.
You can do
whatever you want.
Thank you for being so generous.
Where are you going?
(Wutong House)
Don't be mad.
I'll go back to Shangyin Academy right now.
I won't be angry
if I don't see you.
You're going back now?
Not to spend the New Year at home?
I made it for you in person.
Take a look, at least.
I've seen it.
I'm not a kid anymore!
You all want me to take over North Liang!
Have you asked me if I want to?
Who are you to say no?
Everyone should have the right to decide how to live his life!
You know nothing!
Your life is totally wasted!
You can't even see your responsibility!
Why are you here?
I heard that you tried to kill Xu Fengnian again.
You're afraid to admit it?
Yes.
I did try to kill him.
Let me warn you.
Don't forget who you are.
Well.
A maid can't assassinate the son of a lord?
I'll say it one last time.
If you hurt Xu Fengnian,
I'll throw you into a well
and close it.
You'll just rot in the well
and never see the sun again.
If you understand my words,
write it down
and swear
that you will never try to kill Xu Fengnian again.
Okay.
You want me to write it down?
Bring me a brush.
The bigger, the better.
Remember what I said.
I, Xu Weixiong,
am a person
of my words.
What a coincidence,
so am I.
(Xu Fengnian)
Miss Weixiong rode away
and left Lingzhou.
She came and left like the wind.
It turns out
she came all the way back
just to scold me.
Miss Weixiong has high expectations for you.
She is the first prodigy
at Shangyin Academy for decades.
I'm no match for her,
and I don't want to learn it.
Did Jiang Ni write it?
Um.
Her handwriting is good.
Chen Zhibao.
You should have learnt a lot
at Shangyin Academy.
Why do you care
what I learnt?
You've learnt so much,
but you are still so brutal.
I think Shangyin Academy is a good place for you.
So?
So, you don't need to come back to North Liang
if there is nothing important.
Do you think I'm the cause of the chaos?
Father.
Chen Zhibao left the camp alone
and stopped Miss Weixiong outside the city.
Um.
Father.
Should we dispatch soldiers?
They haven't seen each other for a long time.
Don't disturb them.
(Jiang Ni swears to kill Xu Fengnian)
Why do you want to see me?
Where is the mark of Dahuangting?
There is no mark on Wang Chonglou
when he doesn't use his force.
What is this?
It's Wudang's Treatise of the Most Exalted One.
Hong Xixiang gave it to me.
It's for you.
I don't have Dahuangting.
I'm too lazy to read.
Why don't you read it to me?
Don't even think about it.
I'll give you one penny
for each word.
One penny?
One penny for each word.
Two pennies.
Just one penny.
(Treatise of the Most Exalted One)
If you read more books,
it can still cost me all of my money.
There is more than one book?
Think about it.
I want to learn martial arts,
so, I have to read books.
Let's just use this book as an example.
I asked Hongshu to roughly count it.
It's about 6,000 words.
After you read the whole book,
I'll pay you seven strings of pennies
to make a good start.
It's to your profit.
(Treatise of the Most Exalted One)
Pay me every time after I finish one book.
Okay.
There was something undefined and complete,
coming into existence before Heaven and Earth.
How still it was and formless,
abstruse and profound,
standing alone.
Too rigid.
Read it with emotions.
There was something undefined and complete,
coming into existence before Heaven and Earth.
Be more sedate.
What do you want?
I pay you to read for me.
Shouldn't you read it well?
I'm going out now.
Keep reading
and think about
the best way to read it.
I'll listen to it when I come back.
Your handwriting is good.
It's okay.
My second sister snapped at you,
but you swore to kill me.
Is that appropriate?
Xu Weixiong cares about you the most.
She wouldn't care if I swear to kill her.
She cares about me?
She came all the way back
just to scold me.
That's because she is too disappointed in you.
Why does she
want me to take over North Liang so badly?
What question is that?
My second sister hates
the inheriting system the most.
She wants me to take over North Liang
certainly not for continuing the bloodline of the Xu family.
She must have other reasons.
Then why don't you want to take over
North Liang?
I don't want to see
people keep dying for this thing.
But if you don't do anything,
doesn't it mean that they die for nothing?
Where are you going?
♪ The flower of pain ♪
♪ Blooms in my heart ♪